So I could have said this, but I really like how this person in my comments said it.
And so I'm going to read their words.
Two things can be true.
Cuba and Venezuela are dictatorships.
And we know that is not why the U.S. government has interfered, invaded, manipulated, bombed, extracted, etc. from them or any other.
The U.S. government has never cared about morality when it comes to foreign policy.
Only imperialism and colonialism.
And that does not mean that Cubans and Venezuelans have not suffered tremendously.
And, by the way, that also does not negate from how much Cuba, not Venezuela, has accomplished in terms of health or education and how much more it could have achieved without an embargo.
All of these things are true.
¿Verdad todo?
La Spanish.